♪ In a not too distant future ♪
♪ Way down in deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Mr. Regular Joe they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment needed a good test case ♪
♪ So they caught him on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him into space ♪
-Sit me down!
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ From the worst we can find ♪
♪ He'll have to sit and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ Now keep in mind Mike can't control ♪
♪ Whether movies begin or end ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of his robot friends ♪
-Oh!
-Robot rules called "Cambon"!
-Cambon, now you know.
-Jupy, don't circle.
-Cruel.
♪ If you're wondering how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science Theater 3000 ♪
♪ Hi ♪
[thunder]
-We need now some dark in the bed.
-I need something more. -I need this thing right here.
-Mike! Mike! Mike! -Oh!
-Hi, everyone. Welcome to the satellite a lot.
-What are you doing? -That's Mike.
That's Mike and I'm Tom Servo.
That's about all we can say for right now,
because we are escaping!
-Hey, I found this extra fuel tank to help with the--
-Shh! You escaped.
-I'm going to go and get a new one. -I'm going to go and get a new one.
-We're going to live at Jellystone Park, aren't we, Mike? -I want to go to the gasp
-with a great American hot dog experience. -I would really like to go to Japan
-and see the turtle called Gabara. -Oh, don't forget to pet the Kit Kat bars.
-You know, you can probably just get him an Earth gift shop. -Hey, hey, hey,
-Ixnay, Otis Bay. -Major Nelson, what are you doing?
-Nothing. -Okey-dokey, Smokey.
Well, here's the thing I thought of, Mark.
Many is the time that I've been purposely striding through a major department store
when suddenly, right in the middle of ladies lingerie, I'm accosted by the perfume lady.
-Good afternoon, sir. Can I entice you with a sample of Lebedonis?
-A sample of Lebedonis? -And two.
The next time you're sampled, sample back with my designer line of Mace Moose.
[Screaming]
You see, Mark, just the scrimps of Satan's jocks trapped in the trick.
And my designer moose also comes in Velvet Cudgel, Delirium, and Essence of Detroit.
-Oh, Frank, you also get a free sample of our bath gel. -Here you go.
[Screaming]
-You're a good man. -Oh, my God!
Listen up, Mad Mads. Dig this, Babylon sisters.
Mike Nelson, Tom Servo, Crotea, Robot, and Gypsy are out of here.
That's right, we masterminded our own escape. Listen up. Nobody owns Mike Nelson.
You got that? Nobody! All right, fire up the Liquid Rock Aeryonsters.
I believe it's time for us to fly!
[Screaming]
No. Oh, boy.
Huh. Well.
[Laughing]
You see, you guys, our invention then is a little skit based on what would happen if our escape plan failed.
Oh, Nelson, so close and yet so not.
Your movie this week is Teenage Crimeway. It's a documentary of some sort about the likes of Todd Bridges and Dana Plato.
Frank, you really should layer your mace so it lasts and lasts all day.
[Screaming]
This isn't locks the liquid oxygen. This is locks the fish product.
Well, no reason why it shouldn't work. You sure you're operating that thing right?
Yes, I'm operating.
[Screaming]
Oh, boy. Hey, we're having a crime wave, a teenage crime wave.
12 Angry Teens.
[Singing]
Wow, sex and buff 'em in the same settings.
You're a frowl.
You know, you just leave that gun laying around, some kid's gonna pick it up and start playing with it.
But that's their right.
Yeah, man.
[Singing]
Oh, Elvis Costello's backup band.
Oh, and Sears, huh? Straight off the rack.
[Laughs]
Oh, okay, this is about the rise of plaque and tooth decay.
[Singing]
Excuse me, are you done?
Yes.
[Singing]
Oh, teenage youths, as opposed to the teenage elderly.
You're gonna have to read the whole movie?
Yeah, they said they were gonna make this book into a movie, but this is...
Buy guns. Guns are good. Buy them. Get guns. Buy guns.
Hands-on treatment and da-da-da-da. Yeah, but for now, don't pick at it or scratch it.
Remember to disinfect your teen every day.
And now, back to our gun already in progress. Buy guns.
Come for the pictures of fish. Stay for the house wine.
[Singing]
Ooh, Mia's not doing too well, huh?
Mmm, Bosco.
I'm the guy with the pushed-in face.
Where should I look? Hey, there's...
No, I'm not Judy Card.
Excuse me, are you the only woman in this bar?
The suit is made of pressed oatmeal.
Hot dog!
Any chance you'd want to sleep with a lumpy-faced old guy?
Why don't I buy us a carafe of chabless?
Love me.
What's on your mind, mister?
Just wondering what a sweet kid like you is doing here all alone.
Looking for Mr. Blambauer.
Well, if it's of any interest to you, I was waiting for my date.
His enormous face falls.
Looks like he stood you up, huh?
Wow, she's smoking a dowel.
- Hello, me. - He's only an hour late.
See, I was just at the stubby-cay auditions.
I enjoy us.
Ooh, she's protruding.
There goes an evening.
All dressed up and no place to go.
Is that Shakespeare, mate?
Must be a middle case.
The guy that stood you up, I made.
Now, if that would have been me, I'd have been here on time.
Have you ever seen me on MacGyver?
Maybe it's fate.
What?
Fate, you know, like something brought us together.
Maybe my lack of personal boundaries.
You wouldn't believe in it?
If you do, I got a car up the street
and I know just the right places for a girl like you.
The back seat.
Why not?
That's the girl.
I'll show him he can't stand me up.
Of course.
Boy, oh boy, good thing I brought my life savings with me.
Yes, sir, seven grand in cash and mixed securities.
Wait a minute.
My lucky day.
Oh, boy.
My car's just up here in the next block.
Oh, uh, mind if we drop by my apartment for a minute?
It's just around the corner.
I love you.
You know, it's just like I was saying.
I just took one look when you sat down
and I said to myself, "Freddy boy, this is your kind of girl."
Yes, sir, she's a money-kinderback and a lot of life.
That's the thing a lot of life.
Come on, it's a free dental check.
Quit pawing me.
What is this, anyway?
I thought Terry said you were a real doll.
Just because you take me to a movie doesn't mean you'll own me.
Hey, right on, woman.
What a blind date.
The feeling's mutual.
You can tell Terry I don't think much of her friends.
Well, we made some real progress in the session.
She's like the self-aligned one.
Whoa.
What are you gonna do?
Come on, I told you, dinner, movie, and a mugging.
I'm gonna make you real happy.
Oh, you let me out.
Shut up, get down.
Oh, when's the last time you washed these pants?
Hey, where is this place of yours?
They're just about there for everyone.
Hey, what is this?
Stop it. It's my date.
I want you to do it, Mr. Stanstil. Nobody gets hurt.
Boy, you dirty little trap.
This will teach you not to pick up girls.
And that's for calling me names.
Help! Help!
And that's for yelling "help."
I saw his wallet. He's low.
Ew, he's really moist.
Uh-oh.
Come on, Terry, get going.
At this point, it's more of a teenage crime ripple.
Well, now everything looks to be an order here.
Move along, then.
I'll hold them. You go after the others.
None of this would have happened if they had just used the club.
Who are they? Who are they?
What are their names?
We don't know their names. We never saw them before.
What about you?
Well, I'm, I'm Rand.
You're a helpless.
I didn't know what they were going to do.
You've got to believe me.
You didn't know what is this act.
Every word I told the judge was the truth, Mama.
Court appointed parents.
I didn't know what Terry and those boys were going to do.
You were out with those hoodlums.
No decent girl would be seen with them.
Oh, but I'm not even going to pay them that.
You said you were going to the movies.
Didn't say anything about being with boys you didn't even know.
You're a slutty gun, Mama.
Dad, all I did was go out on a date.
Satan's plaything.
I didn't know what it was getting into.
She came to work and asked me if I wanted to be the nice boy.
Nice boy.
A thief.
Mr. and Mrs. Bridge, reader of the riot act.
You're a virgin.
I wouldn't have been with him if you hadn't picked an argument with me last night.
You sin and you'll pay for your crime, Jane.
I'll be there front row at your hanging.
Daddy, help me, please.
I'm afraid you're going down, kitten.
Hard.
You're my family.
Aren't you?
I don't know how your father will ever face his business friends again.
Let's ask him. He's right here.
Dad.
This is just like dinner at home.
All right.
I got an A in spelling.
If you don't care what happens to me.
I don't either.
What about the rights of that doughy old man?
Jane Kobaly.
Message from the governor.
You're grounded.
Da-da-da.
And here she is, our next prisoner wearing a cashmere sweater.
Jane Kobaly.
One false move, honey. I feel you're full of lead, eh?
Okay, now sit down.
There we go.
I'll just clear the shot here.
Jane Kobaly.
There you go.
I don't like to send a girl such as you to industrial school, but I have no choice.
You have consistently refused to tell us the names of the man who perpetrated the crime.
The fact that you were with men who committed armed robbery makes you an accessory to this crime.
And that fact stands as proof of your guilt.
I'm turning you over to the juvenile authorities, and for your own interest and welfare,
I'm taking you from the custody of your parents.
Honey, we did it, yes.
You'll be transported to the Rosedale Industrial School.
And shopping mall.
Where you will serve a minimum stay of one year.
Then it's off to sunny Hawaii.
It's only a couple of days before parole.
Depending upon your record.
That's a hard face.
Honey, this is your second conviction for armed robbery.
So we're letting you go.
It is my duty to turn you over to the juvenile authorities at Rosedale,
where you will stay until your 21st birthday.
At such time, you will be transferred to the state penitentiary for women.
To serve a term of five years.
Until you are dead.
Until you are eligible for parole.
Depending upon your record.
Now this is a shower room.
Let the movie begin.
It's to clean you up on the outside.
Even if it doesn't get to the dirt inside.
Robin Williams is Mrs. Brubaker.
Stop crying, Annie. That shock didn't hurt that much.
So what was the spinal tap?
We want you to be nice and clean before we turn you over to the industrial school.
There, I've said my piece.
All right, the three in front. In you go.
Let's take it from the top.
You're not fully clean. You're not singing.
Over there. It's de Forest Kelly.
Wow.
Oh yes, the part I love best. There we go.
Susan Hayward in, I Want to Shower.
You might as well snap out of it, kid.
You're in for a while and this isn't going to get any easier.
Do you mind if I hang my Snoopy poster?
All you've got is a year.
Me, I knew I'd had it when I walked into that court.
Pretty neat. We got a Southern exposure too.
Look kid, I like you. You know that.
You could have given the cops a lot more information than you did.
Don't touch me.
What's the matter? You're afraid you might catch something?
Get this through your head.
In jail, nobody's better than anybody else.
And you won't have your mother and father to fight for you either.
That was low.
You're going to learn to listen to me when I talk to you.
Why, kid, don't touch me.
And if you think anybody fights my battles, try me and see.
You little crook.
Jane Cavali, taken down by a left hook, right there.
Oh.
That's one glorious stand-up in Helen Gurley Brown
comparative ideologies that happens.
I had come in a tracwider.
No, no, my belugr to Father's Row.
Let me show you for crying out loud.
Here comes the floppy arm of the law.
No one knew you would be the one who started this.
Uh...
Well...
Two of a kind.
You guys are icky.
I don't want any more trouble, Marsh.
We've got ways of fooling you off.
And that's where you'd go right now
if they weren't taking you out of here tomorrow.
And pick up your room.
So settle down, ladies.
Fools.
Facts of life, go as telekotrass.
Sorry I tried to kill you, baby.
Tonight at juvenile hall, the immature orchestra in prison.
That was a rotten sale.
We're two ladies.
I'm kidding, you're going to prison.
Slim Whitman, chauffeur.
[Humming]
But I really blossomed in senior year.
I quit wrestling.
Then you just check off whether you want lethal injection in the chair.
After you get used to it.
You're lucky we're not driving on down the road to that women's prison.
It's no country club, believe me.
I know. Let's play the quiet game.
I never understand how you kids get yourself fouled up with the law.
Where were your folks, anyway?
I think we lock up the wrong people.
Thank you, officer platitude.
Who do you like in the game tonight?
He's got a real dick Godier quality to him, doesn't he?
[Humming]
Because you never get a second chance to make a first impression.
Lucy, I'm coming.
Hey, this is a no caper zone. Hey.
Big wheel Rossi, the motion picture.
Jeez, I'm sorry, my insurance company is--
Oh, he's got an odd screen.
Wow.
She just whacked out on her Roosevelt.
Well, we better call the industrial school and let him know we'll be late.
All right, get out of the way.
Should I bring my purse? I'll bring my purse.
Oh, she's dead on her feet.
Well, she's had a long day.
Ooh.
Let me go, please, let me go!
I wonder a lot of trouble to spring you, now get out back there.
Can I at least put on some flats?
Keep an eye on her, too.
You try to get away again and you're going to get some lead.
Ooh, I've heard lead is bad for you.
Hey, an old hot dog.
That was a mint stuck to a Kleenex.
Be careful, those who support those young men.
That lipstick makes you feel better, that little taupe.
Hey, this is gray.
Now I'm ready for a crime wave.
Here, what's that taste like?
It's my turn in the front this time.
She's got a load of potatoes.
Gotta get this sheep out of here. I'll ditch it.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, I got car sick in the back seat.
Too windy back there for you?
Just tell me if it gets too windy, because I like it real windy.
Well, the day's taken a real turn, hasn't it?
I'm hurting you.
A little luck there won't be an alarm for an hour.
We'll be 50 miles away by then.
Let me stay here, please, Terry.
I don't want to keep running the rest of my life for something I didn't do.
You're in this and you stay in.
So, how are you kids doing, huh?
Cars in a gully over there. They won't find it so easy.
Oh, either loves or he's hungry.
It hurts to love him.
Oh, honey.
You knew I wasn't going to let them put my baby away, didn't you?
I wasn't worried, Mike, but let's get out of here.
We rented a mountain cabin so far from the boondocks they'll never find us.
How's it going to bring us some money and clothes and heaters?
You'll meet us there just as soon as we phone them.
Get moving, big eyes.
Okay, fat ass.
Well, we made it. 35 minutes away and this is a big country.
It's being in the pen, doesn't it, baby?
Bellman, Louise and Steve.
Let's make a big score and go to Honolulu, huh?
Oh, Mr. D'Wheel again.
Yeah, we can go any place you want to.
So, is the heat off a little?
I'd be a panic in one of them grass skirts with red flowers in my hair.
Also, we interrupt this program to bring you a news flash.
Pop, convenience news.
One hour ago, a gunman stopped a sheriff's car which was delivering two teenage girl criminals to prison.
Killed Deputy Sheriff Jeff Manley and severely injured Police Matron Agnes Hardy.
The gunman bound and gagged the matron, placed her in the car with the dead deputy,
and drove the vehicle into a gully in Antelope Valley near Lancaster.
Police woman Hardy was able to give the authorities a complete description of the car and the gunman,
who is dangerous and well armed.
For further details, keep tuned to this station.
Can we turn our knob to Bob?
That's the end of us.
The end of you, you keep talking that way.
Oh, I knew I should have taken care of that matron.
Oh, we do now.
Oh, then we'll never get through to Al.
Why we can't get through to him? I have no idea.
I gotta find a hole and crawl into it.
Nah, that's stupid.
First thing we gotta do is get off this main highway.
Yeah, now to just rush out with traffic.
Yeah, and I really should have been homecoming queen, but my name got taken off the ballot at the last minute, and that...
Man, this place is crawling with cows.
You want a piece of me, Elsie? Come on!
That's where we're going.
Well, we just passed it.
Climbhouse, we just passed.
We're gonna turn around, right? Shouldn't we turn around?
Is that what you call a blasted heath?
I'll just park it over here.
Maybe I'll park it over here.
I think over here is a nice place. There we go.
Alright, come on. Get out. Get out.
Okay, okay.
But will you be back to pick us up or not?
Here, you stand over here, right there.
Here we go. Does this have a parking brake?
Whoa, whoa, whoopsy! Oh, whoa, no!
Wow!
Hmm.
How are we gonna get away without a car?
Don't damn stupid dump, dump.
They pick us up in a couple of hours.
Leave it to me, baby.
What's gonna keep the people in the house from calling the police?
I am.
Look, look, just move along. I'll do the thinking.
Super action hips.
Wait up, carry me.
Thanks for pushing the car in the gully 70 miles from where we wanted to go.
What's this mess?
Lost Tis Ranchos?
That's this munchies?
You know, I'd like to get a home out in the country, but they're always so far away.
Doe guys, in this four-way, the first person to suffer actual physical harm was the big Doe guy.
And let's never forget, he lived in an era that would forever be known as the golden age of the Doe guy.
Yes, from 1931 until 1959, Doe-iness was a symbol of success.
Proof positive that a man could order 16-ounce quarter-hound steaks for lunch,
and three martinis, tipsy and pink, Doe-ey guys roamed the land freely.
The major politicians of that era were all Doe-ey guys.
Their weight and moisteness were felt everywhere they went.
The most powerful man of that era was the ultimate Doe-ey guy, J. Edgar Hoover, who was not afraid to be a Doe-ey gal.
During that era, Doe-ey men covered the continent. Statistics proved there was more humidity at the time.
Thousand Island dressing was sold by the barrel full pork sausage by the metric Ton-Wai-Wi-Oh,
and the very existence to the fact that our mothers were actually willing to make love to Doe-ey guys.
In tribute to our nation's Doe-ey guys, we now present an honor roll of the great Doe-ey guys.
Past and present, can-boss if you please.
Yen-de-doe-ey guys, doobity-doe-ey guys,
the Doe-ey guys, buttery Doe-ey guys.
The Doe-ey guys of the world, we take our belts off to you.
[chanting]
[music]
Oh, kids, what can I do for you? Have a flat or something?
Come on in, Pa. Give us any trouble. Nobody gets hurt.
You don't need a gun to come in here, son.
But you have to wipe your shoes. Come on in. I was just not talking to my wife.
Can I get you something?
Please be careful. He'll shoot.
Well, he got some extra zagini here if that's what you're after.
Yeah, that's right. You do as you're told. Nobody's going to get hurt.
You cross us up.
The old lady's dead. Am I getting through to you?
I'm thinking it over.
If you harm my wife, I'll kill you.
This is like an elderly strada.
Don't make me harm, Pa.
We'll do anything you say. Tell them we'll do anything they say, Tom.
All right, sir.
We'll do anything you say.
How many rooms you got in this place?
Just this here and two bedrooms.
And, of course, the rumpus room.
Anybody else live here with you?
No. Well, Franz leaves.
What about company? You expecting anybody to come here?
My son.
Mike Tyson.
That him?
No, he's actually more three-dimensional.
Where's he now?
He goes to an agricultural college upstate.
This is coming home tomorrow for the Thanksgiving holidays.
I hope he's got sense enough not to start any trouble.
Well, let him.
That's one thing I can handle.
He won't cause any trouble.
How long are you planning to stay?
Until we get work.
It's not a problem. Are you getting tired of us already?
We'll let you know how long.
Probably just through the high holidays.
It depends.
Well, if you're planning to spend the holiday, I'll need some help.
Mother, no.
Father and I always set a full table.
Big deal, holiday.
Don't you believe in them, child?
Well, sure.
Every day is going to be Thanksgiving from now on.
Well, we'll need a lot of turkeys.
I'll help if I may.
Thank you. What's your name?
Susie Sikophon.
Jane.
Hey, go on over there and sit down.
Okay.
You keep them covered while we look around.
Right.
Sit down, doll.
You're the one.
You might as well know we got a murder up against us,
so we got nothing to lose.
Well, I just put up some peach preserve.
She's so crazy, she just might do it.
You can use that phone to call the cops,
or you can tip them off to us when they come prowling around.
But Mike and I aren't going to be taken alive.
I'm stoic.
Believe me, that's level.
That goes for you too, little flower.
You're in this just as deep as we are.
I saw Mike kill a man.
I'll be a witness to it if I ever get the chance.
Remember that.
Oh, that's right. We should kill you then.
All of a sudden, you got things to say.
What makes you think you'll ever get a chance to be a witness?
Fascinating, Captain.
Anyone for gravy?
Go ahead.
Make my-- oh, sorry.
You'd be doing me a favor.
Well, that's different.
Try me again.
Later.
I gotta say, this isn't anything like the time we had
the Symbionnes Liberation Army over here.
I hope he doesn't look at my fine washables.
There's a whole nother room in there.
There's a window in that bedroom where you can watch
every approach to the house for a mile.
We picked the greatest baby.
I'm on a total high about that window.
Hey.
You guys rotate crops?
Hey, what's that down there?
Storm cellar.
We use it for a storage room.
There's an East Village coffee house down there.
Right down there?
Yes. There's a switch on the wall there behind you.
Really a mess down there. Sorry about that.
You really put up a lot of pickle tomatoes this year.
I've smelled enough.
Don't! Don't do that!
Well, we killed about five seconds.
The car pulls up. We have some company.
We all go right down there.
Take little Grandma with us.
She's my grandma?
And Pop?
You can either forget we're there.
Or you can squeal on us.
Deal with her.
I can tell you right now, I wouldn't do anything
to put my wife in danger.
Not even to see that you get what's coming to you.
Well, then, we're all going to get along just fine and dandy.
Oh, there might be some tension at first.
Well, I'm just a child. I'm hungry.
Come on, Grandma.
You want to help? Go ahead. You're the domestic type.
Better get a couple of those fryers out of the icebox, Tom.
And plenty of milk.
They're just downright impolite.
It's not a farmer. It's the country ain't it?
I like milk.
He's got a bum stomach, nerves.
And take it easy on the seasoning, too, Grandma.
I wouldn't waste seasonings on you thugs.
Huh? What's it doing?
That means something. I know it.
That's our ring.
If we don't answer, it's going to make a lot of people
might be suspicious.
That's a party like a dozen hicks listening in.
That means we can't take a chance on phoning out.
We don't need to call us hicks, son.
We may live in the country, but...
What would you say?
Oh.
Hello. Tom Grant speaking.
Hello, Dad. This is Ben. How's everything?
Oh. Fine.
Good. I'm just clearing up here
so I can leave for the farm first thing in the morning.
Anything special you want me to bring home, Dad?
What? Can't think of a thing, son.
I just thought I'd check to see if you forgot anything.
How's Mom?
I'm being held hostage. She's fine.
Then we'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah, we'll expect your home about 11.30.
All right, son. Goodbye.
Help!
Ben says hi and don't have fun till he gets here.
Isn't that real cool, Dad?
You keep that up. The only one who's going to get it in the next, the turkey.
Don't mock turkeys.
Why a waggon?
You got a real nice tablecloth here, Pop.
And I ought to get Al out here.
What'd you tell him?
They get a car and pick us up.
Here.
A couple of high crews.
Want to play Scrabble or something after this?
Ow, ow, ow.
Richly satisfying.
Pop, your chairs are too hard. You know that?
Don't mark my chairs too, son.
Too old-fashioned.
I listened to Snoop Doggy Dog. Does that help?
You ain't hospitable, Pop.
I'm a Midwesterner. What do you want from me?
You're going to get a visit from a salesman, you know that?
Not Herbalife again.
Only this guy, we don't hide from him.
He's invited.
I got a hand up to you, Mike, the way you use your head.
Here's your paycheck.
Hey, little flower.
Your boyfriend, Al.
If he stopped, he's a salesman. Call on a customer.
Yeah, how about that, Pop?
You would've said, "Buy a chicken feet.
First-class stuff for your charge."
You want to unpack that one for me, son?
I'm going to take this away. That's what you want, ain't it, Pop?
So, what do we mail this letter?
It's a box out on the road.
What does that put in the city?
Tomorrow, I suppose.
All right, Pop.
Come on. Give me company.
Well, I think we need some time apart.
I get a loan, so I need a lot of company.
After you, Pop.
I'm not a violent man, but if you take my last stamp, I'll kill you.
So long, Sarah. I'll send help.
No much about farm cooking?
No, I don't.
Well, it's bland, and there's lots of it.
We can ourselves. Even churn our own butter.
In our pants.
We live simply.
I'll send you next to copy. The farm is almanac for that.
I get it, Bant.
It wouldn't hurt you. I need to learn something about a kitchen.
What makes you think I couldn't handle it if I wanted to?
There's a churn with a hand dasher over there.
Plenty of cream if you want to help.
Oh, no. You got it wrong. You're working for me.
Can I have the day off?
Want to know something?
I used to cook whole meals for families.
Wow.
That's right. Me, little Terry.
No higher than that.
They had me washing and cooking and scrubbing all the time.
There's a difference between working for strangers and working in your own home.
What do you mean, strangers? My sisters.
Four of them.
Each one taking me on for what they could squeeze out of me
and passing me on to the next one.
Now, cry me a river, dear.
Check that fairy tale, Cinderella. No kidding.
Scullery maid. That's what I was.
Where were your parents?
Six feet under.
Oh, they were miners.
Accident?
No, thanks.
Yeah, real accident.
They were almost as old as you are when I was born.
How's that for breaks?
Oh, my God. That's old.
So don't give me any of this bunk about the home.
Also, you're my share of cheap.
Born in the wagon of a traveling show.
That way I'm saving my nail polish for the ball.
I change from scullery maid to Cinderella.
And midnight ain't never coming.
I think you lost your allegory. It's off the track.
What are you doing to that chicken? Cream-aiding it? Hurry it up.
Well, I'm extruding it if you don't mind.
Hey, Mike, you think they'll talk about us on television?
Big shots now.
They don't get it.
Stick with us, little Eva.
You'll be able to buy your own butter already made up.
No kidding.
We'll be rolling in loot.
What are you going to do with all the money you didn't get for killing that deputy?
You talk too much.
I've been wondering, Jane, you weren't really with him, were you?
No.
I just happened to be in the wrong place at the wrong time.
Why don't you close your yap?
Shut your pie hole.
Doesn't make any difference.
Nobody believes it anyway.
I sure don't.
I think I do, Jane.
Okay, so you believe her.
I can stop wondering so much.
You wonder about us country folks.
We wonder about your city folks.
Could I have some pie?
You're selling.
You don't need a gun with an old man like me, son.
You don't trust anyone, do you?
Am I that transparent?
That's right. I don't.
Let him talk. Go on, Pop.
You're really going to set this part of the country on fire.
Guaranteed.
Just like Jesse James.
Famous.
Yeah, that's right, Pop.
Shh.
You're not going to get shot in the back.
I feel sorry for you.
You want to know something, old man?
I'm thinking the same thing about you.
Isn't that weird?
What have you got on us except age?
A milking machine, for one.
You don't even live to be old, Terry.
Somewhere, someplace, in some lonely corner,
they'll find you out and kill you.
Cut it out!
Trying to watch the war wagon.
Short life, huh?
Would you shh, please?
A free ride.
Take it easy.
Don't let it choke, son.
I'm going to get it.
And I'll be right behind you, baby.
Were you going to be a little Eva behind the cow?
No, Vassar.
We interrupt this program to bring you a special news broadcast.
The man in your living room is a criminal.
A statewide search has been instituted by law enforcement agencies
to apprehend two teenage girls and a youth
who killed the deputy today in a successful break for freedom.
Seriously injured two was a police matron
who was taking the girls to a penal institution.
Who am I?
The governor has branded this crime as one of the worst
in the state's history of juvenile delinquency.
Wow.
Juvenile crime, the governor said,
is spreading at a dangerous rate
and is rapidly reaching the point where it must be dealt with harshly.
Roadblocks have been set up to cover all highways and roads.
I can't believe you lost the remote.
I should never have turned in the Rosenbergs.
From leaving the state, this is the killer, Mike Denton.
Two prior arrests.
He is five feet nine.
Wait, about 160.
Brown eyes.
Black hair.
Cute.
Scar on left cheek.
Take no chances, this man is armed.
He's got a post.
I think I must have got a college.
This is Terry Marsh.
A second conviction for armed robbery.
He's profiled.
She is five foot four.
Wait about 105.
Blonde hair.
Blue eyes.
Haba-haba.
She is armed.
This girl is also dangerous.
Dig that profile.
This is the third member.
Blonde.
The victim of armed robbery and assault.
She has black hair.
I look so fat.
Height five feet two inches.
Wait about 101.
A lot of talent to go to Wastonary Form School.
All residents of the Antelope Valley are asked to be on the--
Don't see Scott.
Sugar anyone?
I'm going to--
Please, Mike, don't do anything to us.
Shut up, wait.
I'm going to the office.
It's that thing again.
Why?
What does it mean?
Well, either hit her or I got to get the phone.
It's his ring.
Come on, Pop.
Do like you did before.
Okay.
The hostage farm family.
Congrats, Biggie.
Hello, Tom.
Thought I'd stop by and pick up that seed catalog.
See that gal on TV?
Wow.
Oh, the seed catalog.
Well, I'm afraid I misplaced it, Bill.
I'll help you find it.
I'll be right over.
Bill, I'm too busy helping Sarah to spare the time right now.
Anything wrong, Tom?
No, it's just Sarah.
She hasn't been feeling too good.
You're plumbing, you know.
Then I'll have to say goodbye now.
You didn't tell me you had a seed catalog, old man.
I'm going to kill my wife.
I told her to keep out of it.
You're just a scared little coward with no more courage
than a rabbit.
Here's my courage.
Go on.
Probe an eight.
Maybe your boy Sergeant will be the hero.
Yeah, I like him with medals.
And I like him buttery, too.
Oh, that meal hit hard.
We'll take turns hitting the sack.
When I get sleepy, Michael, be right here
with one eye on the road and the other on you.
So don't be making any plans.
Oh, stars, we don't get out much anymore.
Will you hand me the book, child?
Sure, Grandma.
What are you reading?
Women Who Run With The Wolves.
Well, wouldn't you know?
I haven't cracked a Bible for a long time.
Wow, lots of love, Moses.
Well, everything nice and neat, all written down.
Married Thomas Paul Grant to Sarah Kilton Wayne.
February 28, 1910.
That's private.
Born and son, Benjamin David.
November 29, 1927.
Hey, I didn't know I could read.
Say, that makes him over 27.
That's kind of old for college, ain't it?
Yes.
Stupid, huh?
I couldn't make it the first time.
Well, yes.
No, Terry.
As a matter of fact, he's there on a scholarship.
His education was interrupted by the army.
They blocked his path to the classroom.
You were only a young girl then.
I was never very young.
Always grown up.
I'm younger than that now.
Les Goren was also interrupted.
I was a young girl.
There have been some changes made.
I like them.
Where's Mom?
I'm Mom now.
Yeah, Mother's all right.
That hide-in-the-room thing worked so great.
She'll be just as long as you behave yourself.
All right.
What do you want?
Well, a telegram, huh?
Don't do anything to make them mad, son.
Please, just do as they say.
Now I know who they are.
I've seen their pictures in the papers.
Well, how do you like that? We rate.
I'll tell you how you rate. You're a bunch of hoodlum.
It sounds like a hero.
Better button your lip, Buster.
Don't start anything, Ben.
They'll only be here a while long.
We only stand once a year. Let's be nice.
That's good news for the old lady.
Uh, think of us as guests, fella.
From the fraternity.
Yeah, alpha-kai boner.
Take the old lady in the bedroom.
Hey, little junior, easy to get along with.
Come on, grandma.
Don't worry, mom.
And I think I'll take your car keys just in case.
You might want to take the car to a party.
Hey, you work out. What's your mix?
Is that just former?
Someday I'd like to take you apart.
Put your legs where your arms are supposed to be
and place them for some.
I used to have cartilage.
Whoa!
You'd like me to take it out on your old man right now.
Right before your eyes.
Oh, I can't stay mad at you.
Ow!
All right.
Shut up and sit on.
He didn't say anything.
This is just great.
I'm not going to get any studying done this weekend.
Do you have your newspaper with you?
There's one there someplace.
Did you read Judge Parker yet?
Oh, I love Anna Quindlin.
Oh, they're playing this up.
Hey, little flower, your picture's in here.
Do I look fair? Listen to this.
The father of Jane Coberlain, one of the escapees,
told this reporter that his daughter
was an innocent victim of circumstances
and engaged a prominent attorney to reexamine the case.
No.
Innocent victim of circumstances.
I get it.
How do you do?
It is believed that the trio may have slipped across the border
into Mexico.
Olay.
Mexico?
The thirties have been alerted apprehend them.
How do you like that for a break?
I won! I won!
You're up, Les Bonoli.
Well, that's where we are, Mexico.
What's what it says here?
I'm confused.
This, uh, this he and his crime.
Hey, college boy, what does that mean, he and his?
It means you stink.
Oh, thanks.
Now, where did that come from?
That was completely uncalled for.
(HUMMING)
Oh, ki-do-ki, Mr. Vocabulary.
What does pistol whip mean?
(HUMMING)
I made bars.
I helped.
What happened?
Hero, looking for action.
Go on, hero. You just keep needling me.
This was a Walmart frame.
Bingo! Out!
This movie is 40 minutes of hard driving, living room action.
I'm all faced so that I could remove mountains and have my charity.
Just a pig.
I haven't ever seen a pig before.
I just saw all my goods to feed the poor.
And though I give my body to be burned and have my...
Are you sure the postman picked up that letter?
He got it, Mike. It's on its way.
Howdy, you know. You only saw it from the window.
Charity and be a thorn.
How do you know he's a pulling a stunt?
Relax, Mike.
Does not behave itself...
Put you right to yourself!
He's not easily provoked.
Thank you, Snowy.
Hey, give me a smoke.
I'm all out.
Uh, cigarettes know nothing when to dump.
Nuts around here.
Hey, got any more?
You used up what I had.
Here's a butt.
My luck. I have to take over the Christian Science reading room.
Hey, Pop, you got your day's makes the same Sunday.
When I was a child, I spake as a child.
I understood as a child, I followed as a child.
When I became a man, I put away childish things.
I lost my spot.
Now I got to start over in the beginning
that God created.
What do you do around here for excitement?
I lost my spot.
I'm a lady who sit around and read the Bible.
Now I know what it is.
What do you do for laughs, you know?
I got a copy of the Talmud.
You're a guy like you, all right, muscles.
You firm pectorals.
You make out with all those cute little hayseeds around here, huh?
Why did you go to all those dances?
You wear your big medals, huh?
You're being very inconsiderate right now.
What about you, baby?
How about you, baby?
You go for his muscles, huh?
I'm more of a butt girl.
Sure you do.
All things got a weakness for muscles.
I said he was your type.
You didn't go for him.
He's respected. He's got an upbringing.
He's even got an education.
It's a pity you didn't have any.
That's what you're wrong, sunshine.
I went to DeVryde.
All the education I need is right here.
To kill innocent people?
To kill or be killed.
Like an animal.
Yeah, like an animal.
I don't beg for bones anymore.
I get kibbles and bits in my bowl.
I got plenty of education.
When I was young, when I counted.
No.
Good thing it was, too.
Made me see things the way they are.
Chocolate.
You don't look out for yourself.
Nobody else does.
You're sick.
And you're twisted.
Yeah, I'm sick.
I'm sick of hanging around here.
That's what I'm sick of.
I'm going to tell these guys about it, too.
A guy like me needs a lot of room.
No reason we can't all get along.
Being swirled.
Stuck with each other for a while?
How much longer are you going to stay?
Long enough.
Tonight on "Cryptic Hoodlum."
Honey, can it, please.
Therefore, if I know not the meaning
of the voice, I shall be under him
that speak it up a very long time.
Uh-oh.
And here that speak it shall be a barbarian.
Mike, this is Thanksgiving, right?
Yeah.
So how does Squanto figure into all of us?
Oh, he's coming, I think.
Are you Henry Rawlins?
Yes, now you can dance to the Bible.
Please, please, please, please.
Perfect.
I'm a police officer, not a judge, Mr. Coberry.
All I do is enforce the law.
She had nothing to do with any murder.
She couldn't have.
Not Jane.
I know how you feel.
But we're not equipped to take civilians on a hunt, Mr. Coberry.
But that's just it.
You'll hunt her down.
Don't you see why you've got to let me go along with you, Chief?
I know we're sad.
To let me help her.
I understand.
A Golden Hitler award.
We simply can't take the responsibility
of letting you come along.
Oh, you don't understand.
Nobody likes me.
Once before I made a mistake by not helping her.
She wouldn't be in this trouble
if it hadn't been for that.
All right, I'll prove your love.
All right, all right.
May cost me my job.
Not your worth it.
I'm sending a couple of men
into Antelope Valley in about ten minutes.
That's where your daughter
and the hoodlums were spotted last.
You can go along.
If it'll make you feel any better.
Thanks, Chief.
There, now I'm a pirate.
Arrg.
Pretty jazzy, huh?
How can you even be interested in clothes
when there's a manhunt on for you?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Manhunt.
I enjoy my sleazy-diz.
You're wasting your time
if you're playing him against Mike.
That all it's worrying you?
You'll get him killed.
He's got an odd tan.
You're dirt, Terry.
He'd never touch you.
Don't you call me dirt.
I'm more like topsoil.
Okay.
Well...
I'll show you how dirt operates
on a respectable guy.
Oh, for fun, a science experiment.
I'm worried about our house guests.
(CHUCKLES)
With those potato chips
you put on the top of that casserole.
Yeah, try that one.
And Moses tied his ass under the tree
and walked ten miles...
What you do with the backs of my cards?
I'm not in on all cylinders.
Tied his ass to the tree.
I love that.
Cylinders? What does that mean?
Come on, I'll keep an eye on things.
I need a smoke.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Oh, boy, hot flash.
What?
Want some?
(SNIFFLES)
Oh, can you...
You want to be alone, I suppose.
Well, I'm not very good at these situations.
I'm awkward.
You're going...
Oh, pretty dumb.
Like you're going someplace, huh?
Quit it.
Hey, hero.
How do you like her in your pants?
Well, I don't...
Maaaam!
I like her fine.
Oh, you like her fine.
I'd like to kiss her, Tom.
The cows are going to have to be milked.
They'll spoil otherwise.
All right. Get moving.
Uh-uh.
I'll take them.
What's the matter with you?
I love cows.
I said, I'll take them.
Be my guest.
Put our magic to the test.
(GASPS)
Let's get out of the chair.
Come on.
Dinner ready yet, ma'am?
We'll stay with the dad.
Where do you think you're going?
Get a doctor.
Forget it.
You're the doctor, Miss Florence Nightingale.
Go on, go on, go on. Snap her out of it.
I'll be all right.
The whole idea of her in your pants, son.
Oh, I know what I need to do, Dad.
Come on, Mom. We'll get you in the bedroom.
We've got an old defibrillator in the garage.
Tom!
Back to the Bible, Gramps.
Tell me more about the crocodiles
and that tiny ass to the tree thing.
What got into you before?
You know, it's gotten into me.
Munster cheese.
I don't like anyone giving
my girly eye.
I'll try that on Mother.
Wow.
Well, Pop, you don't have to watch.
Kind of want to, if that's okay.
That was silly of me.
Yeah, that heart attack was downright stupid.
I never fainted before.
I like it.
Don't talk at all, Mrs. Gramps.
Close your eyes, please.
Wait a minute. I smell pumpkin pie.
Mom, remember when you lost all your underthings?
I took them.
No, man.
I can't take it any longer.
But he's waiting for you to try.
Please don't take any chances, Ben.
They're desperate. I know he wouldn't hesitate to kill you.
Hi. I'm desperate and I wouldn't hesitate to kill you.
Go ahead. Give it to him.
Go on, hero.
Mike, please.
I said take it, hero.
You miss.
I kill you, old lady, on the spot.
What now?
Go on. You want to brain me.
What's there to brain?
Take it.
Lay off, Mike.
Oh, no.
If he doesn't, I'm going to bust his face
like he was the bus driver.
We don't want any blasting this week.
No, awkward.
You want the cups to hear the shot?
Put it down, Ben.
Should I be reading the Bible or not?
Or no?
Well, just stand here, then.
Can't we just have a normal Thanksgiving
where we drink and don't talk to each other?
Long day, huh?
Yeah, you said it.
Yeah, I'm disappointed in you, hero.
Glad this movie's not in 3D, Mike.
Why don't you do weigh medals in a poncho?
I'm not a wholestine on wheels.
What say we drive over to the Amish farm
and show them our buttons?
Ha!
Oh, there I see a good parking spot.
Wait, there we go.
Why don't they look?
Tell me, why don't they look?
Somebody drove a car over here.
Nice, muffiny hats there, huh?
Now, you look at that.
The other half of the black dollia.
Now let's keep going.
That's an odd deer stand.
Check the oil, Dave.
Take this down, Smith.
W-dash 6495.
631.
Bingo!
Oh, boy.
Well, feel free to dig through the evidence.
I gave it to her for her birthday last month.
This is a break, all right.
Go straight with my uniform.
They must be around here someplace.
Well, I wouldn't be too hopeful, Mr. Cobley.
Yeah, it's probably dead.
Come on.
Glad I could make you feel better.
The car was reported stolen the day of the killing
in Los Angeles.
We found positive identification.
Let's check some of the farms around here.
By the way, that's a really cute purse, Bernie.
Shut up.
Sir, I'm gonna ask you to make the siren sound
with your mouth.
No man can serve two masters.
Or either he will hate the one and love the other,
or else he will hold to the one and despise the other.
He cannot serve--
What's it saying there by getting the smoke, Pop?
Well, I'll check Ezekiel. Hey!
What she shall eat.
What she shall drink.
How about a miracle, Pop?
You don't know much saying pack of butts.
It's kind of wasting a miracle in the body.
Behold the fowls of the air.
What advice do you got, Pop?
No, Cherry Garcia.
I don't understand.
Get out all that stuff.
And it cleans the oven.
Light up the sky with your name.
Did you ever stop to think that the longer you live,
the more you gotta worry about dying?
It's a fact.
Now you die soon. You don't worry so much.
You lost me, son.
Mike, quick.
Relax. They'll never fit through the trellis.
Carpola conscience turned into the place.
I got a really act now.
You know, you know, come on, get outside.
Get in that cellar.
Well, I've got some canning to do anyway.
Honey, I'm gonna be in the bedroom.
If anything goes wrong up here, you know what to do.
The barbecotch, you know, gets it.
Oh, great. He's on his second pass through the Bible.
Now, don't forget to bring along that cute purse, Bernie.
Come on up, Earl.
Dad!
What are you trying to do,
you little finger?
You're gonna stunk like that, and I'm gonna...
Well, he's goal-oriented.
Prosby stills and hutch.
Howdy, gentlemen.
Hello there. I'm Sergeant Connors.
This is Officer Smith, Mr. Covey.
I'm not a hostage. My name's Tom Grant.
What can I do for you?
Well, you haven't seen some kids around here
answering this description, have you?
Oh, hey, she's hot.
I've been hearing and reading a lot about them, though.
They haven't been here, though.
Keep in mind how nervous I am, though.
You're not in the basement, no.
You'll let us know if you're running to anything suspicious, huh?
Yeah, sure will.
I'd like to use your phone if I may.
I'll have to ask the hoodlums.
I'll be a certain, Sergeant. Right there behind the door.
You look through the barn and the other buildings.
Why don't you go along with them, Mr. Covey?
You might recognize something we've missed, huh?
In other words, bug off.
Oh, there it is.
Thank you.
You have a touch-tone crank phone.
Hello? Give me state police headquarters.
Michigan 239...
You've been getting the role of Curley in Oklahoma.
It was a big triumph for me, because that was the first time...
Your commentator said those kids got through the drag net.
He said they were probably in Mexico by now.
Yeah, don't you get a plow something?
It could be anywhere.
We'll find them.
Yes?
Sergeant Connors on the phone, calling from Antelope Valley.
Thank you, disembodied voice.
Hello, Connors.
Well, we found the car they used to get away.
And a ditch, 30 miles from Lancaster.
And a country road.
Take me home.
Do the place I belong, huh?
Mountain of identification. Good work.
I'll put it on the teletype immediately.
What happened after they left the car?
Well, we're checking around, but it's pretty much spread out up here.
They're definitely not in the next room.
Well, a couple of blood hounds could pick up a trail from the wreck car...
and save us a lot of guesswork.
Yes, sir?
No, we won't search the rest of the house.
We work the farms around here to bring the dogs up.
I like Wade. He's just not a dancer.
Around 7.
Right.
Well, thanks very much.
Those hounds will find out if they're still around.
That wasn't long distance, was it?
Something down there?
I... Oh, no.
Just preserves.
I went down to pick up a couple of jars for my wife.
Hey, that's me.
Next room.
Okay, well, keep your eyes open.
Well, how about you, you trained professional?
Hey, I escaped!
Woo-hoo!
I really need those pants.
Tension, tension.
[Groaning]
You better not be blowing the whistle on us.
Your hand smells like nickels.
Witness protection.
Okay. No identity.
Sounds good. Bye.
Hey, you can kill him now.
I sang like a bird.
I want some of those preserves now.
You've been holding out on me.
Come on, come on, come on, get up.
Okay, okay, okay, I'm up.
Did you hear him?
Yeah, I heard the whole pit.
They bring dogs down here. We're dead.
Woo!
[Singing]
What were you gabbin' about out there?
I told you I wouldn't do anything to hurt my wife.
Oh, you're right. I forgot about that.
We gotta get out of here right away.
How? Why would we use for money?
They must have some.
We have to wait for Al.
Yeah, we wait for the hounds to lead him back here.
How do you know Al even got the letter?
Let's find out.
Ah, you crazy. It's a party line.
We have to take the chance.
Do you need me for this discussion?
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Go on, get on that phone.
Request girl from Upanima.
Call Normandy, 3-00-99 in L.A.
What do I say when I get an answer?
Yeah, I'll tell you what to say.
They got like it's a social call. You're calling your pal.
Then call L.L.D. and order me an anorak.
[Bell rings]
Come on, Ruth.
3-00-99 in L.A.
Oh, the hoodlum looking.
I'm glad you made it home for the holiday.
Nice weather, isn't it?
Yeah, sure is.
There's a dance tomorrow night if you're not doing anything.
No, no, Ruth. Thanks. I won't have time.
I will not be ignored, Ben. Hold please.
Rockbuckers, thank you.
[Bell rings]
This is Jim Rockford.
Leave a message and I'll get back to you.
Jimmy, this is Angel. I'm in real bad trouble.
[Bell rings]
Keep trying until you get it, will you, Ruth?
All right, Ben. Thanks.
I still say we ought to get out now.
We can use the Herald station wagon.
And I say we wait for our-- we need all the insurance we can get.
We got insurance. We got the Herald and the old lady.
Even those all the shortcuts around here.
Don't you hear all?
Zoe knows the shortcuts,
but what good is that? Where do we hold up?
That's something Al's got all figured out.
Look, we get Al on the phone.
We don't have to take a chance.
Al sounds like a real sharp cookie.
We still got him till morning.
Boy, she makes my pants look good.
Nice hinder, son.
Thanks, Dad.
I'm in the girl.
Stop staring at me, you phone.
Guy's not even sexual enough to be a femme.
God, I gotta read the Bible. Just a page.
There's that sound again.
Leave our house. What do you want?
Hands at the phone, or the curtain gets it.
Hello? It's probably for me.
Yes, this is City Band colleague.
Have your number, Ben.
Thanks.
Hello? Hello?
You know what to say? Go ahead and say it.
Hello?
This is Ben.
Ben. Hello?
Did you get my letter?
Letter?
No one sends me letters.
I didn't get no letter.
Jerry Lewis!
Who is this anyhow?
I sent you a letter inviting up a Thanksgiving dinner tomorrow.
Hello?
We couldn't wait for you to get it.
Your blind date's anxious to see you.
So I'm phoning you instead, and we're expecting you tonight.
Hello?
Blind date?
Oh, the teenage crime wave!
Sure, Ben, sure.
Hey, give me that address again.
Just make sure I got it right.
It's the Post Road, Antelope Valley, Lancaster County.
East Jesus, Missouri.
Follow Route 24 straight after the farm.
The name's Grant.
Thomas Grant.
What is the White House with the red barn right off the road?
There's a wooden fat guy bending over, attending the garden.
You might be able to do a little business at the same time.
Pop slow on chicken feed.
Chicken feed?
I'm out of my depth. I don't mess with chicken feed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
I'll come up right to work.
I think I just ordered some magazines.
(KNOCKING)
(SINGS IN DISTANCE)
After all, I'm completely ineffective.
Now you go ahead.
As long as Pop is right where my gun can see him.
Now that I'm Christian Slater.
So, how's everything going in here?
(LAUGHS)
A hundred and one pounds, huh?
How are you feeling?
Oh, you're breaking my wrists.
I have to be getting back to college, Mom.
Big test tomorrow.
Oh, and thanks for the great Thanksgiving.
A hundred and one pounds of fun.
You don't do too high.
Can I go shopping with you sometime?
Don't cry, Jane.
Just keep it inside.
Learn how to hide your feelings.
There's so much hanging over me, Ben.
So much I can't shake off.
You've got to hang on, Jane.
You made me see the sense of it before.
Now's the time, son. Make your move.
Good night, baby.
You can't get away from...
The single set for the last hour.
Um, can I touch your butt?
No, that's wrong. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's plenty of people who brought together
when time is running out.
What are you saying?
Are you a sorceress like all the other women?
Only a few hours.
Do you men always know what to say, huh?
I've done it.
Hello.
- Bye-bye. - Okay, get out. Here's a car coming.
You stay.
'Cause it's really so fun 'Cause it's really so bonds
When you have super fun Eating tasty mints
You can challenge morease You can bend silly rules
You're rebelling in an unthreatening way
You're really blond and it's true People look up to you
When you eat mints Whenever the hell you want to
Youth is better in every situation Youth is better old is stupid
Youth is better so eat mistos And live a super long fun life
Mistos!
Who is it?
It's Bill Salisbury, a neighbor of ours.
- He invented the steak. - Anybody else with him?
No.
Get rid of him.
Remember, Mama Hero?
Ben, don't.
Salisbury's gonna press to see the seed catalog.
- Hello, Bill, come in. - Howdy, Tom.
Ben, I haven't seen you in a dog's age.
- Toss up a couple of plates. - You've taken up a little weight, haven't you?
Glad to see you got back for the holidays.
Say, you'll be showing the whole valley
How to grow giant crops before long.
- I am too, Bill. - Postage.
- Sure. - Pasta.
- Postage. - Sausage.
She's lying down. She's still not feeling well.
Oh, too bad. I'll look in and say hello.
- I'll go put her down. - Oh?
Say, I'm thinking of going hunting tomorrow morning
I was hoping you'd check it over.
I'm having trouble with a shell ejector.
- You're our most dangerous friend. - You know how bad the expert at these things?
I didn't think he'd mind.
What makes you think, Ben, is an expert at those things?
Handled enough of him in the war, didn't he?
He was pushing pencils and Albuquerque.
It's time you got a new one with all the trouble this one's given you.
Uh, mind if I sit down?
I, uh, oh, no, sure.
If you want to.
The police come knocking at your door a while back.
- You want to get high? - They did.
I figured maybe them kids are around here somewhere.
We'd better leave that to the police.
Maybe I can injure myself and draw them out.
How about it, Ben? Find the trouble yet?
Ben is a farmer now, a gunsmith.
Oh, too bad.
I was hoping he'd know what to do.
- That was an empty dream. - Well, thanks anyway.
I guess I'll be getting along.
And I hope that that gun has better aim than I do tomorrow.
Say, Tom, maybe next time I go, you can manage to come along, too.
Holy cow, do you have Rod Serling over for dinner?
It was to be a pretty good shot as I recollect.
You people live like pigs.
Yep, I've seen the time when you brought home some mighty good venison.
- Yeah. - That's fake.
- Get something, Bill. - Put it down fast, bud.
Do what he says, Bill!
- Give me your cigarettes. - I was in some kind of trouble, Tom.
Had a film after the phone call yesterday.
You'd be my tent, wouldn't you?
I said put that gun down.
Somewhere a deer is smiling.
Yeah.
- Make me... - Incovered.
You two get back in there.
Must have been really easy to be a war hero back then.
There.
- I spoke up with you. - Ooh, the crotches of Madison County.
- It's good. - It's good.
Still covered.
We gotta do everything around here.
Take your hostage, drag the corpses.
Geez.
Still got you covered.
Oh, they're gonna put 'em up.
Wonder how they'll pickle.
I should have visited the Johnsons.
You fool!
You didn't have to kill him.
We could have kept him here until Al came.
I don't like you talking like that.
Aw, I don't like this guy anymore.
He's crossed the line.
- I'm sick of you. - Still got you covered.
You're yellow and you're stupid and you're trigger happy.
Let's get married.
You've got us into this and now you can't think straight to get us out.
Look, I was your man when I sprung you.
Don't you forget it.
I thought you were somebody.
But you're only somebody when you got a gun in your hand.
Hello, premise of the movie.
Look, all I want to do is wait quietly for Al to come and get out of here.
That's the smart way.
Holidays are always so stressful.
All right, all right.
Wait.
It's about time.
Oh, God.
Anybody tell you you could take a walk?
You want to eat, don't you?
Cows are in there.
- Gonna eat a cow? - Besides, you've got my money.
I wouldn't walk far.
Oh, come on, snap it up.
But you can't imagine what this feels like.
Ooh, that an anemic cow.
Skimmo.
Oh, the farmer and the cowboy should be friends.
I haven't had a chance to talk to you alone.
All right, go ahead, talk.
Come on, I'm making butter over here.
Watch this.
When they're this full, you just poke them.
Like in the war.
I read about it once in the papers.
Both sides laid down their arms for a night.
It was Christmas.
They even played records to one another across the field.
Snoopy and the Red Baron became friends for just one night.
Enjoy my tummy.
It's a holiday now.
Oh, moo.
You're gonna have to get in line.
There's a couple of cows ahead of you.
No truce, huh?
Mrs. Hoodlum, can I just do my chores?
You know something?
I was all grown up before I saw a barn or a cow.
Cow?
Or a hayloft?
She's making a double Nintendo.
You really hate me, don't you?
Why, you're threatening to kill my mother.
That throws cold water on my lust.
Kind of an answer you expect.
Something with Savage Farm Boy in it.
I don't know.
Guess maybe I got the wrong message, huh?
Don't recall sending a message, Captain.
Too bad.
Some other time you could have felt differently about me.
I'm too sexy for my pants.
Well, it didn't work out that way.
Well, I'll go slap the hogs now.
But in my league, people take what they want.
Working on a sex spot.
I thought it was a truce.
Here's the one you wanted, sucker.
I'm a war hero, and I call you're dead.
Come on, throw it over here.
Please.
You were really playing me for a chump, weren't you?
We're making soft serve. Come on.
I'm bad. I should be spanked with an open hand.
Get moving, Farmer Boy.
I've wasted enough time.
Oh, no, don't, no. Stay.
Don't milk us.
Oh, boy.
A little early yet.
They'll have the dogs up any minute.
Yep.
Anytime.
Dogs.
Car coming.
Yep. Whoop.
Dogs.
Yeah. Stop them. We'll look them over.
If they got any dogs.
Yeah, that should be the dogs.
♪ Come on over, baby, hold on ♪
♪ Huddley, huddley, ho, you guys ♪
♪ Hey, what can I do to do for you? ♪
Somebody hang wrong, officer?
That jacket.
This is the third time I've been stopped.
I'm gonna be late for all my calls.
The fellow's gotta make a living, officer.
You're self-eat.
I came with a car.
Not gonna go?
Cut.
Open your trunk.
Trunk?
What for?
Just open it. That's all.
Well, I guess I just woke up a communist Russia.
I'll get right to that trunk camera.
Oh, a very intimate shoot out here.
Oh, that stung.
That was a gun.
It was a cow.
What if it was the cops?
Maybe they got Al.
We're not gonna wait to find out.
You and Brideyes get your lady out here.
Well, this thing's giving shot.
Look.
Look, careful, careful.
Might be full of rotting gym shorts.
You have to shoot him right in the face, Ted.
He came at me with his face. I panicked.
Hey, did you see the undercover feed salesman?
Go.
Come on, come on.
Well, now it's officially a wave.
It sounded like it came from the grand place.
Oh, hold that loosened me up, oh gee.
[imitates gunfire]
Get an ambulance, baby.
Coach Landry, you need anything?
This has been the best ride along ever.
The best part is we just leave him lying there.
No paperwork. Woo-hoo!
And we are going to have fun this time.
Going on there, turn right for town.
I was you, I'd find some out of the way road to take.
Because if we don't make it--
We don't make it.
[gunshot]
This is it, this is it.
This is life without nothing.
Ever--
[music playing]
ADK to control.
Young FDR.
Hey, maybe there's someone up here
who can shoot in the face, Ted.
Look, lay off.
Lucky shot.
I love that.
Almost milk cows.
[groaning]
They've gone. Which way?
To the right, to the Los Angeles Highway.
They took my wife and son with them.
You better get them to a hospital, Mr. Coveley.
Your finger fits right in your wound here.
[humming]
Jeez, didn't milk the cow four days.
Milk everywhere.
The station wagon leaving the highway.
Turned off on victory, heading for town.
Get out of general alert.
There's a car tailing them now, sir.
How do you like my mustache?
Take the car on the close surveillance
and wait for a break.
Thank God we have radar.
Now keep in touch.
Call every once in a while.
Pass that information on to Connors.
Huh, looks like the cast of grease
missed the activity bus.
There's a pro car up ahead.
So what, they're all over the city.
Yeah.
Really good job finding that out of the way road.
[laughing]
[groaning]
Apparently Grandma doesn't want to go to the home.
Ah, forgot to change my tab.
Sorry, everybody.
I told you not to head back to the city.
You told me.
The only chance we had, I couldn't lost.
Honk, shoo, honk, shoo.
Turn left to the light.
Shall I use the directional?
[laughing]
Turkey will be so dry, it'll be like eating a boot.
Put your shoes on Grandma, we're almost at your house.
Oh, I need Ambersol.
Well, certainly is a nice day for a high speed old car chase, huh?
Beautiful.
Scenic.
Herbie has escaped.
You know, I could drive better if you didn't have the gun on me.
I could relax a little, you know.
Come on, I want to see Bob Hope's house, now step on it.
[humming]
Pull into that parking lot up there on top.
We can lose the cops in the crowd.
Come on.
Watch out for Chris Penn and Robert Downey.
[music playing]
Graham Stoker's car 54.
80K out.
They're headed for the observatory.
[screaming]
Gonna shoot this guy in the face, too?
Don't you just--
Go towards the lights, Bob.
Toward the lights.
Whoa, what are we on, a filter world?
[humming]
Why?
It's the Roddy McDowell Monuments.
Oh, thanksgiving.
Come on, take the other road.
We had two for tickets.
Wow, yeah, let's go to a remote out of the way spot
and blend in with people who aren't there.
Gee.
Oh, I hate people in a park like this.
[humming]
No, I broke a heel.
[gunshots]
[horn honks]
You'll never even live to be old, Terry.
Somewhere or someplace in some lonely corner,
they'll find you out and kill you.
Remember when I said that earlier?
Run, you--
[gunshot]
Yeah, I could get you into college.
[humming]
I could help you get a Pell Grant.
That's the Jiffy Pop Mosque.
[laughs]
[gunshot]
I'm dead.
Oh, no.
You think college credit for life experience.
You're earning a degree right now.
[gunshot]
Oh, right in the shoulder, yeah.
[humming]
So, Dor, you want a taste, too?
[gunshot]
Wait for it.
Society didn't give me enough bullets.
[clears throat]
[grunts]
Luckily, I took a class in observatory maintenance.
[humming]
I, too, took a class in observatory maintenance.
[grunts]
[humming]
Mitchell!
Take it, Ben, miss the hand-to-hand lessons.
[humming]
Fun house.
Hey, they're on the inside of a Judy Chicago major installation.
Hey, great view.
Oh, that's my tetanus arm.
Oh.
[humming]
[laughs]
That's a slinky guy.
Oh, this is how the Hubble got screwed up.
Well, this is my-- stop!
[grunts]
Outside, the police corps marathon passes by.
[laughs]
Stop on my bike, ten-lea.
[humming]
Uh-oh, something to see here.
And all cops take a course in observatory maintenance.
You turn on the AC while you're at it.
[grunts]
Oh, yeah, the Snickers bar.
[humming]
[muttering]
I wanted it spinning.
[laughs]
Babe, oh, honey, come on.
Talk about it.
Just give me one good crack at her.
Let me watch her die.
I want to make faces as she rises in pain.
So you made it after all.
Rot in hell, Tala.
Hey, cop, that'll even ever figure out any of this.
Hey, that's not fair. I helped a little.
We just took her along for the ride.
Oh, don't mean to rush her, ma'am.
This death can take long, thanksgiving and all.
[sobbing]
I'm dying in your son's pants.
Nobody ever cried for me before.
Argentina?
I think she's got more lines, ma'am.
Should I work the mouth?
Look to this day, graduate, as you plunder the world.
[sobbing]
Oh, go ahead. Let it out.
Have a teenage cry wave.
Wow. Now, there's an upbeat ending for you.
Yeah. Zingo.
[sobbing]
Does not justify the means.
Wow, Crow.
That movie posed so many difficult questions,
yet at the same time left so many things unanswered.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So, letters?
Yeah. Right.
Hey, isn't it Tom's turn to get them?
Mail call, mail call.
Oh, brother.
Robot, Crow thee.
Yeah.
They didn't get Squawk, Crow.
My guess is you skew lousy with women and young men.
But we'll put together some focus groups
and ferret that out for you.
Sirbo, can we just have the mail, please?
Keep your flight suit on, Nelson.
And just what kind of a name is Nelson anyway?
You're not russian by any chance, are you, comrade?
Keep those things.
All right. This first one is from,
oh, from Jim Pratt.
Could eat no food?
And why don't you put that up on Stillstore there?
They look the better clean.
Thank you. Jim Pratt.
Okay. Jim writes, "Dear Mike Crow,
Servo and the rest of the MST3K crew,
those of us who just finished watching
the Brain That Wouldn't Die experiment
here at the New Hampshire State Prison
all feel that Mike Nelson has potential."
Thank you. Thank you, Jim.
That's very nice.
Nelson, you got the prison vote.
Yeah. Well, it doesn't surprise me.
Your situations are similar.
Although, I imagine it's a little worse up here.
You know, no visitations, food's lousy.
Everything you know and love is thousands of miles away.
Yep.
But you got us.
That's right.
Isn't there another letter?
I hope so.
Yes, there is another letter.
This one is from Valerie Curiacopolis.
And I have an idea that maybe you could read this one, Tom.
I'll tell you that. I just will then.
Welcome, Mike. I'm glad you're on the S.O.L.
You'll definitely have your hands full up there.
But just remember, even though those bots
have been up there longer, you're bigger than them.
Just keep that in mind when...
You're bigger than some of us, Mike.
Yeah, just remember, Mike, if push came to shove,
I could take you.
Wow.
But I never would.
Oh, my scars!
Well, that's all from our round back down to you,
subterranean doey guys.
That's right. I'm doey man.
I control the world supply of dairy products.
Steak is my ally.
Butter does my bidding.
Sour cream bows down before me in total abject terror.
Onion rings quake at my very...
[screaming]
[growling]
[music playing]
[groaning]
[screaming]
[music playing]
[groaning]
Oh!
[music playing]
[groaning]
Oh, for fuck's sake!
[screaming]
[music playing]
Oh, no, you don't, not this time!
[laughing]
[screaming]
[music playing]
[groaning]
Oh, huh.
TV's Frank, see me.
Dr. Forester.
I wonder what's going on.
Where'd she go?
[screaming]
[music playing]
To be on the other side.
Taylor!